

# **ARSLAN MUNIR**

## Full Stack WEB DEVELOPER

## **CONTACT ME**

0307-1621527

arslanmunir482@gmail.com

arslan-munir

MG-Paratha Revenue Society Johar Town Lahore

## **EDUCATION**

#### **Allied School**

Matric in Science 2014 - 2016

#### **Punjab College**

Intermediate in Computer Science 2016 - 2018

## **PMAS Arid Agriculture University**

BS in Information Technology 2018 - 2022

## **SKILLS**

#### Languages:

- HTML5
- CSS3
- Javascript

## **Technologies:**

- Tailwand CSS
- Bootsrap
- React JS
- Express JS
- MONGODB

## **ABOUT ME**

I am a passionate web developer driven to create cutting-edge, user-focused digital experiences. With 1 years of experience working on front-end websites, I enjoy transforming concepts into useful, eye-catching designs. I aim to utilize my creative thinking and communication skills to add value to your projects.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Freelancer**

2023 - 2024

Frontend Web Developer

- Working as a frontend web developer.
- Convert design mockups into functional, interactive web pages using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Built interactive web applications such as calculators, quizzes, or productivity tools using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Bootstrap.

## **Social Swirl**

2023 - 2023

Internship as a Frontend Developer

- Experience working in a collaborative development environment, including participating in code reviews and team meetings.
- Implement features and functionalities as per project requirements.
- Identify and fix front-end issues under the guidance of senior developers.
- I am starting my internship at Social Swirl as a Frontend Web Developer from August 20, 2023 to October 13, 2023.

## **Projects**

- E-Commerace
- Developed the Frontend of an e-commerce website using HTML, CSS, and Bootstrap to create a visually appealing and user-friendly shopping platform.

## **Projects**

### • Laam Website

 Developing the Front-end of the Laam website using HTML, CSS, and Bootstrap to create a modern, responsive, and user-friendly interface.

#### Microsoft Website

 Developing the Front-end of the Microsoft website using HTML, CSS, and Bootstrap to create a modern, responsive, and user-friendly interface.

#### • Sapphire Website

 Developing the Front-end of the Sapphire website using HTML, CSS, and Bootstrap to create a modern, responsive, and user-friendly interface.

#### KFC Front-end

 Developing the Front-end of the KFC website using React JS to create a modern, responsive, and userfriendly interface.

### • Samsung Website

 Developing the Front-end of the Samsung website using HTML, CSS, and Bootstrap to create a modern, responsive, and user-friendly interface.

## • Black-Camel Website

 Developing the Front-end of the Black-Camel website using HTML, CSS, and Bootstrap to create a modern, responsive, and user-friendly interface.